A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Frank Brink, Jr., Series 6 FA832
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Frank Brink, Jr., Series 6
1961-1978
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Rockefeller University
Brink, Frank
FA832
1.5 Cubic Feet
Arrangement
Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies is arranged into 3 series:
Series 2: Publications. Series 4: Convocation. Series 6: Frank Brink, Jr.
Other Finding Aids
FA224 Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Publications, Series 2.
FA831 Rockefeller University records, Dean of Graduate Studies, Convocation, Series 4.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 380-6
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of the RAC.
Biographical/Historical note
Frank Brink, Dean (1957-1972) James Hirsch, Dean (1972-)
Scope and Contents
Primarily consists of announcements.
Scope and Contents
Primarily consists of announcements.
Medical research; Medical education
- Frank Brink, Jr., 1961-1978; 6; 1.5 Cubic Feet
  Scope and Contents note
  Announcements from Dean's, Bulletin Board. Announcements of courses, lectures, demonstrations, seminars.
  Arrangement note
  Bundled by year.
  - 1961, 1962 (Box 1)
  - 1962, 1963 (Box 1)
  - 1963, 1964 (Box 1)
  - 1964, 1965 (Box 1)
  - 1966, 1967 (Box 1)
  - 1967, 1968 (Box 1)
  - 1968, 1969 (Box 1)
  - 1969, 1970 (Box 1)
  - 1971, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 1973, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Announcements from Dean's Bulletin Board, 1975-1978; 2½" Hollinger (Box 2)